Bixler High Private Eye is a adventure, family, tv movie
film directed by Leslie Kolins Small.
Teenage detective Xander DeWitt is the new kid at Bixler Valley High, and he's there to
unravel the biggest mystery of his life- the truth about his missing father.
But in order to crack this case, Xander must learn to work with a
partner- fearless investigative reporter Kenzie Messina.
Xander DeWitt, played by Jace Norman.
Cara Jean, played by Samiyah Womack.
Charlie DeWitt, played by Ed Begley Jr..
Kenzie Messina, played by Ariel Martin.
Ellen DeWitt, played by Terryn Westbrook.
Female Cop, played by Marissa Morgan.
Bixler High Private Eye is an American comedy
television film that aired on January 21, 2019.
The film stars Jace Norman, Baby Ariel, Samiyah Womack and Ed Begley Jr.
and was directed by Leslie Kolins Small.
The film explores themes of high school, detective, disappearance, school, town.